<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Entries Count="76">
  <Entry Index="0">Basic Controls
◆ Run
→ Tilt the Left Stick hard in any
direction.

◆ Lift the object in front of you
◆ Talk / Examine
→ Press the Confirm Button.



◆ Throw / Give the object you are holding
→ Press the Confirm Button while holding
an object.

◆ Put the object you are holding into
your Bag
→ Press the Cancel Button while holding
an object.


◆ Eat the object you are holding
→ Press the Tool Button while holding
an object.

◆ Use equipped tool
→ Press the Tool Button.
    ※When using a higher level item,
     pressing and holding the Tool Button
     will charge the tool.

◆ Swap equipped tool
→ Press the Left or Right Buttons.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="1">Next, use the Directional Buttons and Confirm Button
to water in the pattern shown by the example.
This will repeat three times.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="2">Use the Directional Buttons to move the Nature Sprite
and the Confirm Button to put food in the Bins.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="3">Am I right in assuming this is the first time you've ever
worked on a farm? Please allow me to offer some advice.&lt;wait&gt;&lt;page&gt;
To talk to a person standing in front of you or lift objects
next to you, press the Confirm Button.&lt;wait&gt;&lt;page&gt;
Next, to use an item, make certain to equip it first, then
press the Tool Button to use it.&lt;wait&gt;&lt;page&gt;
And when you need to do a bit of shopping, go to a store,
stand across the counter from the shopkeeper and talk
to them. However...&lt;wait&gt;&lt;page&gt;
If the store is closed, you can still speak to the
shopkeeper, but you won't be able to buy anything.&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="4">Default</Entry>
  <Entry Index="5">Options</Entry>
  <Entry Index="6">Failed to read downloadable content</Entry>
  <Entry Index="7">Downloadable content data is no longer usable</Entry>
  <Entry Index="8">Checking downloadable content data</Entry>
  <Entry Index="9">Downloadable content data check complete</Entry>
  <Entry Index="10">Obtained additional costume(s) as downloadable
content. Use the Mirror in your house to change.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="11">Account Book</Entry>
  <Entry Index="12">Title Screen</Entry>
  <Entry Index="13">The red berries in the upper-left corner of the screen
represent your Stamina. It goes down when you do things
like use tools.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="14">The face icon in the upper-left corner of the screen
denotes your level of Fatigue. It changes the more
Fatigue you build.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="15">To grow crops, first you must till the land with a Hoe.
Equip a Hoe and press the Tool Button.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="16">Land with objects on it can't be tilled. To clear the
ground, cut Weeds with a Sickle, or pull them by pressing
the Confirm Button.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="17">Stand near a chicken and press the Confirm Button
to talk to them.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="18">Stand near an Angora rabbit and press the Confirm
Button to talk to them.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="19">Stand near a cow and press the Confirm Button to talk
to them.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="20">Stand near a sheep and press the Confirm Button to talk
to them.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="21">Stand near an alpaca and press the Confirm Button
to talk to them.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="22">Stand near a foal and press the Confirm Button to talk
to them.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="23">To fish, equip the Fishing Rod and press the Tool Button
to cast the fishing line straight in front of you.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="24">When a fish bites, the bobber will move violently.
Press the Tool Button at that moment to reel in your
fish.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="25">Press the Confirm Button repeatedly to have the Nature
Sprite harvest Turnips.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="26">Press too fast, and the Nature Sprite will try too hard
and start to sweat. If this goes on for too long, they will
fail.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="27">When they start sweating, slow down the speed at which
you press the button and let the Nature Sprite rest.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="28">Press the Confirm Button repeatedly to speed up your
horse. But be aware: the faster they run, the faster
they'll lose stamina.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="29">When the bubble is red, no matter how fast you press the
Confirm Button, your horse won't speed up.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="30">Your horse will recover stamina whenever you are not
pressing the button.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="31">Balance your horse's stamina carefully by pressing the
button at just the right time and race to first place.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="32">Press the Confirm Button to cheer on your chicken.
Cheering for them when they cluck may startle the other
chicken.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="33">When the game begins, the cursor will start to move.
Press the Confirm Button at just the right time to
stop it.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="34">Mini-Games with the Nature Sprites
Let's Play with the Nature Sprites!
[Harvesting]

Have you met the Nature Sprites yet?
Are you becoming fast friends already?
If not, you really ought to get to know them.
If you play with them often enough, they
will be more than happy to lend you a hand.


One of the games you can play with the
Nature Sprites is the Harvesting Game.
Repeatedly hit the Confirm Button to have
the Nature Sprite harvest more and more
Turnips. 

The key to victory lies in how fast
you press the button. If you hammer on it
for too long, the Nature Sprite will become
sweaty and start having a hard time.
At the end of the game, mistakes are
subtracted from your overall score as
negative points. Once a Sprite's face becomes
sweaty, simply leaving them be won't return
them to normal. Instead, when you see
that telltale sign of exhaustion, don't let
up on the Confirm Button entirely; press it
much more slowly to let them rest. 
Give this game a try and show the world
what an agricultural ace you are!
Let's Play with the Nature Sprites!
[Feeding Chickens]

Are you best buds with the Nature Sprites
yet? They won't play with you unless you
are. There are lots of benefits to being
friends with the Nature Sprites, not the
least of which is that warm and fuzzy
feeling you're sure to get inside!

One of the games you can play with the
Nature Sprites is the Feeding Chickens
game. In this game, a Nature Sprite will
feed five chickens while you pay close
attention to each bird's behavior. If you
don't keep a watchful eye, those crafty
cluckers will fly the Coop before you can
say "omelette du fromage." Also, be careful
not to feed a chicken while its Bin is full.
Otherwise, it will just get angry.
At the end of the game, mistakes are
subtracted from your overall score as
negative points. Watch each chicken, and
when it looks like one's Bin is starting to
empty, quickly have the Nature Sprite fill
it back up. Keep in mind that you do not
need to put feed in every single Bin.
It's up to you to devise your own strategy
for keeping your avian amigos fed in
record time!
Let's Play with the Nature Sprites!
[Watering Crops]

Are you constantly relying on the Nature
Sprites to help you with work? Remember,
they're friends, not field hands! Make sure
to chat with them and give them presents
so they don't feel like your friendship is
one-sided.

One of the games you can play with the
Nature Sprites is the Watering Crops game.
Move the Nature Sprite and have them
water the indicated rows in the indicated
order. Each round of the game will have
three patterns. If you can memorize when
to water where, you'll be sure to rack up a
high score. But be careful! Water out of
sequence, and the Nature Sprite will not
be a happy camper.
At the end of the game, mistakes will be
subtracted from your score as negative
points. Also, if you mess up the order, any
rows watered after the mistake won't count.
If you feel like you're in over your head,
take a moment to think and remember the
correct pattern. Also, each round of the
game has three patterns, so even if you
mess one up, you will have a chance to
make up for it. Keep fighting until the end!</Entry>
  <Entry Index="35">Festival Tips and Tricks
☆Derby Tips and Tricks

Every Spring and Autumn 18, a Derby
will be held in Rose Plaza. The mayor will
visit your house the morning before race
day to let you know about it, so if you own
a horse, feel free to saddle up and join in.

However, keep in mind that only fully mature
horses are eligible for entry. 
During a Derby, pressing the Confirm Button
will encourage your horse, making it run
faster. However, if you simply mash the
button, your horse will soon tire itself out.
The trick is to use it sparingly, at just the
right time.




If you decide to buy a racing ticket, don't
always play the odds--it's fun to root for
the underdog (underhorse?) sometimes!
But most of all, it's important to raise your
horse with lots of love and care. Practice
riding often, and you will be running like
the wind before you know it.

With the help of this guide, you, too,
can jockey to become a Derby Champion.
☆Cluck-Cluck Clash Tips and Tricks

Every year on Summer 7, the Cluck-Cluck
Clash is held in Rose Plaza. Rick will visit
your house the morning before festival day
to let you know about it, so if you own a
chicken, feel free to join in on the action.



However, keep in mind that you can't enter
the Cluck-Cluck Clash with a chick. Only fully
mature chickens are eligible for entry.

During the Cluck-Cluck Clash, you can press
the Confirm Button to cheer on your chicken,
causing it to startle the opposing chicken.
Whichever chicken turns tailfeather and
runs out of the ring first loses.

The most important factor in the Cluck-Cluck
Clash is your chicken's motivation. If they
aren't feeling the Clash fever, they won't
pay attention to your cheering.

A chicken's motivation is closely tied to its
affection for its owner, making a good
relationship very important. Raise them
with lots of TLC, and soon your bonds of
companionship shall render you undefeatable.
With these nuggets of wisdom held closely
to your breast, we are sure that you, too,
can become a Cluck-Cluck Clash Champion.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="36">Fishing
Once you have a Fishing Rod, an entire
world of ichthyological excitement awaits!

☆How to Acquire a Fishing Rod
Rumor has it that one of Zack's old buddies
used to have a real thing for fishing. If you
talk to Zack, maybe he'll be able to help.



☆How to Fish
Equip your fishing rod and go to a body of
water that seems like it might have fish.
Press the Tool Button to cast your line.

Then begins your fishy vigil. Patience!

When you get a bite, the bobber will bob up
and down drastically. From there, quickly
press the Tool Button to reel in your catch.
If your catch gets away, don't fret. Simply
wait patiently for the next bite. There are
times when you might press the button in
time, but the fish still escapes. Don't give
up. Steel yourself and cast your line again.
Certain bodies of water won't have any fish.
If you find yourself waiting and waiting for
what seems like forever without any bites,
try moving to a different location.

☆Fishing Spots
There are various fishing spots all around
Mineral Town.

◆The Ocean
  You can fish from Mineral Beach.

◆Downstream
  You can fish in the river flowing through
  Southside and across your farm. 
◆The Spring
  You can fish in the Spring next to the mine.

◆Upstream
  You can fish near the bridge behind the
  mountain. (It's a very small spot.)

◆The Lake
  You can fish at the large lake behind the
  mountain. 
◆And more...

There are other little fishing holes tucked
around Mineral Town. Find them and you
may be able to reel in something truly
unique!</Entry>
  <Entry Index="37">Saibara's Forge
◆ Through the magic of metalworking, you
  can buy and upgrade the tools needed to
  take care of your farm and animals here.
  But that's not all--Saibara's place is also
  your one-stop shop for accessories and
  Makers to help you "make" the most of
  your animal byproducts.



◆ Hours
  10:00 AM - 4:00 PM

◆ Closed
  Thursdays





☆Upgrading Your Tools
 ◆ Upgrade your tools and you will unlock
  "charge skills" that you can use by holding
  down the Tool Button. Charge skills will let
  you use the tool's ability over a wider
  range, or break tougher objects.
 ◆ To upgrade a tool, first put the tool and
  the ores required to level it up into your
  bag. Then, go to Saibara, talk to him over
  the counter, and request an upgrade. 
 ◆ While Saibara is working on the upgrade,
  the Forge will be closed, and you won't
  have access to your tool. But once his
  work is finished, the Forge will reopen and
  you can talk to him to get your upgraded
  tool. Make sure you have an open tool slot,
  or you won't be able to pick up the item.



◆ Tools that can be upgraded:
- Hoe
- Sickle
- Axe
- Hammer
- Watering Can
- Fishing Rod



◆ Time required to upgrade a tool:
  How long it takes to upgrade a tool
  depends on how many levels you want to
  strengthen it by at once. Reworking it from
  low to high level in one fell swoop will take
  longer than if you do one level at a time.




◆ The cost of upgrading a tool:
  How much an upgrade will cost depends on
  what level it is being upgraded to. Higher
  levels will cost more than lower levels.

◆ Tool experience:
  A tool's experience points will determine if
  it is ready to upgrade or not. Open the tool
  menu and press the Tool Level button to
  see what level it can be upgraded to. 
☆Tools For Animals
◆ Brushes
  Bristly tools used to maintain the coats
  of cows, sheep, alpacas, and horses.
◆ Milker
  A tool used to milk adult cows.
◆ Clippers
  A tool used to trim the coats off sheep,
  alpacas, and Angora rabbits.

☆Accessories
◆ Bracelets
◆ Necklaces
◆ Earrings
◆ Brooches

These may make nice presents for
someone... They require 1,000G and
a piece of Orichalcum to create, and
take two days to be made.
While Saibara is working on an
accessory, the Forge will be closed.
It will open again when the item is ready.
Talk to Saibara to retrieve it, but make sure
you have an open space in your item slots.





☆Makers

◆ Mayonnaise Maker
A machine that will make Mayonnaise
just by putting Eggs into it. The higher
quality the Egg you put into it, the higher
quality Mayonnaise you will get.



◆ Cheese Maker
A machine that will make Cheese just by
putting Milk into it. The higher quality the
Milk, the higher the quality the Cheese.

◆ Yarn Maker
A machine that will spin any animal Wool
or Fur into Yarn. The higher quality the
byproduct, the higher the quality the Yarn.

◆ Butter Maker
A machine that will make Butter just by
putting Milk into it.


◆ All four Makers cost 20,000G apiece.
They require Adamantite and take 5 days
to create.


While Saibara is working on a Maker,
the Forge will be closed. It will open again
when the item is ready, but you can kick
back and relax, because these babies
come with free delivery! Makers will
automatically be placed in your Coop or
Barn. You can only commission Makers
once you have renovated your Coop and Barn.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="38">Settings</Entry>
  <Entry Index="39">Controls</Entry>
  <Entry Index="40">Button Presets</Entry>
  <Entry Index="41">Button Presets</Entry>
  <Entry Index="42">Restore default settings?</Entry>
  <Entry Index="43">That key or button has already been mapped to
another function. Would you like to switch it?</Entry>
  <Entry Index="44">Please press the button or key you would like to assign.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="45">Toggle the heart icon on or off on the dialogue screen.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="46">Toggle the character portraits for dialogue on or off.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="47">Controller Settings</Entry>
  <Entry Index="48">Open Settings Menu</Entry>
  <Entry Index="49">Key Config</Entry>
  <Entry Index="50">Examine / Hold</Entry>
  <Entry Index="51">Put Away</Entry>
  <Entry Index="52">Use Tool</Entry>
  <Entry Index="53">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about moving around the map!"

"All right. Let's touch on some more basic movements.

☆Auto-run: When you press and hold the Auto-run Button,
your character will run forward in whatever direction
they are facing. ...And that's about it."

"What, can't you change directions?"

"Of course you can change directions! Just turn in the
direction you want to go, and voilà."

"Huh."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="54">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about moving around the map!"

"All right. Let's touch on some more basic movements.

☆Sidestepping: When you press and hold the Sidestep
Button, your character will move around in whatever
direction you press, all while continuing to face forward.
...And that's about it."

"Huh. Wow. But when would you need to walk all funny
like that?"

"Well, it can be rather handy when you're, say, watering
seeds, tilling a field, or even harvesting your crops.
It helps you keep a nice rhythm without a lot of turning
about."

"Aha! That makes sense. I think I'll try that!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="55">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about moving around the map!"

"All right. Let's stick with the basics and go over some of
the buttons you will use:

☆Confirm Button
You can press this button to:
- Talk to others
- Examine objects
- Pick up items

...And that's about it. Oh, and on a side note, if you happen
to talk to another person while holding an item, you'll give
that item to them as a present."

"Huh. Can you give them anything at all as a present?"

"No, there are some items you can't give to others.
You know, important things, like mementos and such."

"Aha."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="56">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about moving around the map!"

"All right. Let's go into a little more detail about the
things you can do using the Confirm Button.

Pressing the Confirm Button will let you examine places
that look like they may (or may not) have something to
investigate. Things like, say, signs, walls, shelves, and such.
Just walk up to the spot you want to check and press the
Confirm Button. Of course, even if a spot looks like it
MIGHT have something, if there isn't really anything
there, you won't be able to examine it.

Picking up objects is similarly straightforward.
There's only so much a person can lift, you know."

"So no hefting huge boulders and trees and stuff, huh?
Got it."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="57">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about moving around the map!"

"All right. Let's go over more of the basics and discuss
another of the buttons you'll use."

☆Tool Button
You can press this button to:
- Use the item you have equipped

"...And that's about it. If you have an item equipped, you
simply need to press the Tool Button to use it. Of course,
if you don't have anything equipped, nothing will happen."

"Oh, I know about this! You can equip stuff like crop seeds
and animal breeding kits, but they will all go away as you
use them. Stuff like tools don't go away, so you can use
them as much as you want!"

"True. You can use tools over and over again, but doing so
uses up your Stamina."

"What happens if you run out of Stamina?"

"I'll tell you more about that tomorrow."

"Okay!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="58">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about the stuff from yesterday!"

"All right. I left off on mentioning that using tools
repeatedly drains your Stamina, I believe. But actually,
I think I'll save the lesson on Stamina until after we've
finished going over basic controls."

"Aww, really?"

"Yes. Now, let's talk about another of your most
fundamental buttons: the Cancel Button. 

Press this to put away the item you are holding. Keep in
mind that this only puts away what you are holding in
your hands, not what you have equipped."

"Oh, okay. Makes sense."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="59">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about stuff you can do!"

"All right. Let's go over some more basic things you can
do on the map, starting with opening the Menu Screen.

When you press the associated button, the Menu Screen
will pop up. The icons you will see are, starting from the
left:
- Settings
- Farm Information
- Items
- Journal
- Tools
- Map
- Relationships

First, let me explain your Journal...which I will do
tomorrow, since we're out of time."

"Okay."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="60">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Teach me more about the stuff from yesterday!"

"All right. Let's continue with more basics: the icons on
the Menu Screen.

We can start with the left-most icon, the Journal...or,
now that I think about it, perhaps we should go over the
basic Menu Screen controls first. It's quite simple. Press
the Confirm Button to open the screen corresponding to
the icon you have selected. Press the Cancel Button to
back out of the Menu Screen and return to the map. 
It's that easy."

"That's it? Really?"

"Yes indeed. Tomorrow, I will tell you more about
the Journal."

"Okay!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="61">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Whatcha gonna teach me today?"

"Today, I think I'll get back to teaching you about all the
things you can find in (or add to) your house.

Let's start with the Journal. You may have already
noticed that it has the same name as the Journal option
on your Menu Screen. In much the same vein, you can
examine this Journal to save or load your game."

"Oh, okay! But wait...wouldn't it just be faster to bring
up the Menu Screen and open the Journal from there
instead of walking all the way to your house...?"

"Urk! S-Sometimes speed doesn't matter, all right?
This helps set the mood and atmosphere,
so it's a perfectly viable alternative!"

"Whatever you say..."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="62">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Whatcha gonna teach me today?"

"Today, I think I'll teach you about the Calendar. This is a
handy item that will let you see which notable events are
happening in a given month."

"How do you use it?"

"Examine the Calendar to bring up the Calendar screen.
Move the cursor around and select the day you want to
view, then press the Confirm Button to open a screen
with details on all the events happening that day.

Any day that has an event will have an icon on it visible
from the Calendar screen. What kind of icon it is will give
you a general idea of what the event may be. Oh, and to
exit the Calendar screen, all you need to do is press the
Cancel Button."

"Consider that jotted down!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="63">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Whatcha gonna teach me today?"

"Today, I think I'll teach you about the TV. The TV has
several different channels, each of which shows a
different broadcast with its own value, educational or
otherwise. 

There are four channels to watch:
- Weather
- Education
- Entertainment
- News

You can change channels even in the middle of a program,
so if you decide a show isn't your cup of tea, you are
under no obligation to watch it to the end. If you decide
you aren't in a TV-watching mood, you can turn the TV
off by pressing the Cancel Button."

"Tele-rific!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="64">Life on the Farm
ADVANCED TIPS

"Hey, Sis! Hey, Sis!"

"Yes?"

"Whatcha gonna teach me today?"

"Today, I think I'll teach you how to navigate around your
Fridge and Cabinet.

Not that there's much to teach. It's rather simple. Move
the cursor to what you want. Press the Confirm Button
to select things. Press the Cancel Button to back out.
Ta-dah.

If you hover the cursor over an item and press the
Confirm Button, you can swap it with whatever is in the
slot directly opposite of the one it's currently in. Oh, and
on this screen, you can also decide to simply discard an
entire stack of items in a given slot."

"Why would you keep around something you don't need,
let alone enough of it to make a huge stack? Well,
whatever..."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="65">∀∀Beginning∀∀∀∀∀∀∀
∀∀∀Life on the Farm∀∀

"Bro! Hey, Bro!"

"What is it?"

"It looks like my Turnips are fully grown now.
What do I do?"

"Face the fully grown crop and press the Confirm
Button to pick it up and harvest it. For Turnips, the soil
will return to its tilled state after you pick it up, and for
crops with multiple yields (like Cucumbers), it will start
sprouting again."

"Wow, so there are crops you can harvest multiple times!
I'm gonna try planting one of those next."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="66">∀∀Beginning∀∀∀∀∀∀∀
∀∀∀Life on the Farm∀∀

"Bro! Hey, Bro!"

"What is it?"

"I can't break Stumps."

"Did you upgrade your Axe?"

"I worked super hard and managed to turn it into a
Copper Axe."

"Are you charging up when using the Axe on a Stump?"

"Uh? I'm just mashing the Tool Button."

"Hmmm. So when you're trying to destroy things like
Stumps or Boulders that require more than one hit,
you need to power up by holding the Tool Button
when using it."

"Aha!"

"By the way, if you're trying to break a Stump with a
Copper Axe, you need to charge up and hit it six times
before it will break."

"Whoa, that sounds hard."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="67">∀∀Beginning∀∀∀∀∀∀∀
∀∀∀Life on the Farm∀∀

"Bro! Hey, Bro!"

"What is it?"

"We were talking about Chicken/Rabbit Feed yesterday,
but where exactly do you get the Feed FROM?"

"Oh, right. All I really told you was where to put it, huh?
There's a Dispenser in the Coop, and if you press the
Confirm Button in front of it, you'll be able to take some
Feed out. By the way, you can take out Fodder in the
Barn in the same way."

"Aha. Now I can finally feed my chicken."

"You've only been letting it out to graze until now, huh?"

"Guilty!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="68">∀∀Beginning∀∀∀∀∀∀∀
∀∀∀Life on the Farm∀∀

"Bro! Hey, Bro!"

"What is it?"

"How do I use a Fishing Rod?"

"You're equipping it and pressing the Tool Button to use
it, right?"

"Yeah, but it just comes right back to me."

"Are you using it at a place where you can actually fish?"

"Huh? Are there places where you CAN'T fish?"

"You need to use it in places where there's water,
like the river, ocean, or mountain lake."

"I was trying to throw it inside my house and at a tree.
Was that wrong?"

"Y-Yes...? I...can't believe I have to clarify that. You can
only catch fish in bodies of water."

"But I want tree fish! Treee fiiish!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="69">∀∀Beginning∀∀∀∀∀∀∀
∀∀∀Life on the Farm∀∀

"Bro! Hey, Bro!"

"What is it?"

"I tried using the Fishing Rod, but I still can't catch
any fish."

"For the love of-- Did you press the button again once
when the bobber got tugged?"

"No. I was staring at it the whole time, waiting for
something to happen."

"When you get a hit and the bobber gets tugged, you have
to press the button again to reel your catch in."

"Ohhh. So just leaving it in the water won't do anything."

"Right. And sometimes, even after you pull it back,
you won't have caught anything--or worse, all you'll
have caught is garbage--so keep trying until you get
a fish."

"Okay."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="70">∀∀Beginning∀∀∀∀∀∀∀
∀∀∀Life on the Farm∀∀

"Bro! Hey, Bro!"

"What is it?"

"The town is so big that I still get lost sometimes."

"When you get lost, open the map from the Menu Screen.
You can see where everything is, including your current
location. It might help you remember the layout of the
town, too."

"Okay."&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="71">∀∀Beginning∀∀∀∀∀∀∀
∀∀∀Life on the Farm∀∀

"Bro! Hey, Bro!"

"What is it?"

"So there's a map, right? But it only tells you the names
of stores."

"Incorrect. If you place the cursor over a building and
press the Tool Button, you'll be able to see more detailed
information on it. If it's a store, you can even see when
their business hours are."

"Whoa, that's convenient!"&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="72">※Watch out! Press the button at any time other than
when you're turning a page or choosing your answer, and
you'll skip right past the question! Be patient!&lt;wait&gt;</Entry>
  <Entry Index="73">To mount your horse or speed them up, press the Confirm
Button. To dismount, press the Cancel Button.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="74">Turn the vibration function on or off.</Entry>
  <Entry Index="75">Vibration</Entry>
</Entries>